Theresa Wolfson Papers 5216
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI. Pamphlets
  - Pamphlets - Signed by Authors (Box 74)
    - G-H, 1946-1968 (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 1: Gershoy, Leo - Carl Becker on Progress and Power, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 2: Goldman, Ralph M. - The Advisory Referendum in America, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 3: Goldman, Ralph M. A Transactional Theory of Political Integration and Arms Control, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 4: Gross, Feliks - Russian Political Emigration of 1948, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 5: Gross, Feliks. The Planner and the Planned, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 6: Gross, Feliks. XXV Parallelism and Progress, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 7: Harris, Abram L. - The Scholastic Revival - The Economics of Heinrich Pesch, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Item 8: Hurwitz, Samuel J. and Edith - The New World Sets an Example for the Old-- The Jews of Jamaica and Political Rights 1661-1831, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - J-K, 1948-1966 (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Item 1: Jacobson, Sol - College Professors and Income Taxes, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Item 2: Jonas, Paul - Henry Luce and the Anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Item 3: Klarman, Herbert E. - Income Tax Deductibility, 1948; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Item 4: Kublin, Hyman - What Shall I Read on Japan..An Introductory Guide, 1954; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Item 5: Kublin, Hyman. Takano Fustataro: A Study in Early Japanese Trades - Unionism, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - L-M, 1939-1958 (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 1: Ladejinsky, W. - Agrarian Unrest in Japan, 1939; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 2: Lasher-Schlitt, Dorothy - Josef Schreyvogel, Grillparzer's Vaterlicher Freund, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 3: Meiklejohn, Alexander - What Does the First Amendment Mean, 1953; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 4: Miller, S.M. - The Concept of Mobility, 1955; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 5: Mushkin, Selma - Financing of Unemployment, Cash, Sickness and Workmen's Compensation Insurance, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Item 6: Mushkin, Selma. The Fiscal Capacity of the States, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - N-O, 1947-1956 (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 1: Nathanson, Jerome - The Ethics of Inheritance, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 2: Nathanson, Jerome. John Dewey: Some Reflections, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 3: Nathanson, Jerome. The Reconstruction of Religion, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 4: Nearing, Scott - Fascism, Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 5: Neufeld, Maurice - Appunti Sul Funzionamento Delle Commissioni Interne, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 6: O'Neill, J.M. - Church and State, Three Studies, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Item 7: O'Neill, J.M. The Separation of Church and State, 1947; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - P-R, 1925-1963 (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 1: Palmer, Gladys - Job-Conscious Unionism in the Chicago Men's Clothing Industry, 1930; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 2: Palmer, Gladys. Trade Custom in the Lancashire Cotton Industry, 1928; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 3: Parshley, J.M. - H.L. Mencken: An Appreciation, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 4: Perlman, Mark - Organized Labor in Hawaii, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 5: Perlman, Selig - The Labor Movement, A Theory of, 1949; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 6: Petshek, Kirk R. - Employment As An Element in the Wage Bargain, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 7: Powdermaker, Hortense - The Channeling of Negro Aggression by the Cultural Process, 1943; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 8: Reich, Nathan - Collective bargaining: The U.S. and Germany, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 9: Rischin, Moses - The Jewish Labor Movement in America: A Social Interpretation, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 10: Robinton, Hermann F. - A proposed Regional Public Records Plan for New York State, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Item 11: Robinton, Madeline R. - The Lynskey Tribunal: The British Method of Dealing with Political Corruption, 1953; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - S, 1935-1969 (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 1: Senger, Gerhart H. - Social status and Political Behavior, 1945; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 2: Salvemini, Gaetano - Can Italy live at Home, 1936; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 3: Saposs, David J. - The American Labor Movement Since the War, 1935; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 4: Schapiro, J. Salwyn - The Age of Uncertainty, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 5: Schwartz, Harry - Agricultural Labor in the First World War, 1942; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 6: Schwartz, Harry. Farm Labor Adjustments After World War I, 1943; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 7: Schwartz, Harry. Hired Farm Labor in World War II, 1942; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 8: Schwartz, Harry. On the Wage Structure of Agriculture, 1942; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 9: Schwartz, Harry. Recent Developments Among Farm Labor Unions, 1941; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 10: Seligman, Ben B. - The Impact of Positivism on Economic Thought, 1969; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 11: Sellers, Rose Z. - A Different Drummer: Thoughts on Library Education, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 12: Sturmthal, Adolf F. - Foundations for World Organization: The Experience of International Working Class Organizations, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Item 13: Sugitani, K. - (Japanese title), Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - T-W, 1937-1962 (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 1: Takagi, Yasaka - On the Principles of Democracy and Other Essays, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 2: Tead, Ordway - Collective Bargaining and Personal Freedom, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 3: Tead, Ordway. Industrial Relations 1939 Model, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 4: Temple, William J. - Serviceable Speech in a Democracy, 1947; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 5: Volin, Lazar - Agrarian Collectivism in the Soviet Union, 1937; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Item 6: Wood, Austin B. - Transference in Client Centered Therapy and in Psychoanalysis, 1951; Pamphlet (Box 74, Folder 29)
- Series VII. MISCELLANEOUS
  - Includes index cards, term papers, clippings, notes, personal and miscellaneous, Pamphlet (Box 75-78, Folder All)
- Brittle - Theresa Wolfson Italian labor unions chart, Pamphlet (Box 79)